# Ivan Alex de Oliveira

City: Salto - State: São Paulo Contact: +55 (19) 9.9248-1225 Email: ivan.indaia@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ivan-alex-oliveira



#### **Objective**

IT Analyst

#### Resume

I am Ivan Alex de Oliveira, I help companies make profits and achieve their goals. I'm graduated in information technology, and I have more than 15 years of professional experience.

I have experience and capacity to act in the functions of Development Analyst, Database Analyst, and IT Support Analyst, always working as a team, excellence, and strong leadership.

I was able to learn and develop strategic skills that provide me with professional growth while maintaining the ability to innovate.

I believe in great purposes, and I do my best in my job, projects, and I'm always willing to lead new challenges seeking out the success.

Every moment I have need to accomplishment, having the commitment to winning the obstacles with confidence, making things happen.

## **Education | Graduation**

Information Technology - emphasis in Computer Network - FATEC/2013

**Intermediary English** 

### **Experience**

TK Logística do Brasil - 05/2022 currently job

Function: Junior System Analist

Projects in systems, ERP(Senior) and TMS (Web Migration), SaaS systems, SQL Server database, documentation (PMO), Implantation of methodologies ÁGIL(ITIL).

# **TK Logística do Brasil** - 04/2018 a 04/2022

Function: Junior IT Support Analyst

Help-Desk, Infrastructure Projects, WMS and TMS System Implementation, Environment Monitoring: Systems, Infrastructure and Back-up, Firewall (SonicWall), Oracle Cloud, Antivirus (Kaspersky), Windows Server, Active Directory, File Server, Access Point, VPN, Office 365, Migration TENANT O365, MFA, AIP, Making Reports SQL Oracle, Act in IT Governance and Security, Restore of Environment Windows, VMWare, CSC(BPM) and GDPR Implementation.

### TK Logística do Brasil - 10/2015 a 03/2018

Function: IT Assistant.

Help-Desk, WMS and TMS Systems Support, Environment Monitoring: Systems, Infrastructure and Back-up, Multifunction and Thermal, Firewall (SonicWall), Antivirus (Kaspersky), Windows Server, Active Directory, File Server, Access Point, VPN, Office 365, Migration TENANT 0365, MFA, AIP, Making Reports SQL Oracle, Act in IT Governance and Security, Restore of Environment Windows, Windows Installation and programs.

Freelance - 12/2011 a 10/2015

Function: Computer Technician

Windows formatting and installation, programs installation, computers montage, network setup, internet, routers, switchs, printers. Maintenance in laptops/desktops/Servers.

#### PROCAM - Gestão de Automação Industrial - 06/2011 a 12/2011

Function: Trainee

Caprind System Support - ERP/MRP/CRM/ISO/SPED/NFE.

### FIEC - Fundação Indaiatubana de Educação e Cultura - 06/2008 a 06/2009

Function: Trainee

Basic Computing Teacher (Windows, Word e Excel).

#### Skills | Courses | Certificates

**Basic**: PHP | Java Fundamentals | Basic Java | WordPress

Intermediary: HTML5 e CSS3 | JavaScript | MySQL | Java POO | Python

**Advanced**: Algorithm

**Currently: WEB Development** 

Contents: HTML, CSS, JavaScritp, Firebase, Jquery, Bootstrap, Node.js, Mongo DB, React Js, Redux,

Router e Electron.

Programming logic, Hardware, BD I e II, S.O., Networking Basics Concepts , Analysis and System Projects.

Windows Server 2008, 2012 | SQL Server, AD, FS, Oracle Cloud, Kasperky | WMS Systems | TMS Systems | SQL | Office 365 | VMWare | HelpDesk, Visual Basic, VPN, Firewall (SonicWall) | office advanced package | Information Security.

# Competence

Capacity to act as Development Analyst, Database Analyst and IT Support Analyst

Identification and orientation in troubleshoot | Preparation and lead in program correction and maintenance activities.

Coding and testing accomplishment | Preparation of documentation and make of operating manuals.

Implementation of new systems maintenance| Adjustment of systems to monitor changes and user needs

Keep security as per company policies | Accomplishment, implementation and maintenance of hardware and software.

Definition of access control to resources | Performance monitoring of installed technologies resources.

Proactivity | Good communication | Assertiveness | Flexibility.